{
    "subject": "resource/Novar_Controls",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Cleveland",
    "human_readable": "Novar Controls is located in Cleveland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8855748772621155,
            "question": "Where is Novar Controls located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229939937591553,
            "question": "What state is Novar Controls located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5174112319946289,
            "question": "Does Novar Controls have offices in multiple locations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5077349543571472,
            "question": "Is Novar Controls based in a major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4876108169555664,
            "question": "What city is home to Novar Controls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4108331501483917,
            "question": "In which U.S. city can you find Novar Controls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3502891957759857,
            "question": "What kind of business is Novar Controls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.257885605096817,
            "question": "Could you find a Novar Controls branch in New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1237163096666336,
            "question": "Is Cleveland known for its manufacturing industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.014874915592372417,
            "question": "Do they have international offices?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Novar Controls is located in Cleveland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_354_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Cleveland known for its manufacturing industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_354_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you find a Novar Controls branch in New York City?",
            "html": "dbpedia_354_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of business is Novar Controls?",
            "html": "dbpedia_354_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_354_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Novar Controls Corp. is located in Cleveland, Ohio, United States. Therefore, the statement \"Novar Controls is located in Cleveland\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}